https://www.familylawyers.com.au/privacy-policy/

Get Started Online
Barkus Doolan Family Lawyers (BD) is committed to protecting our client’s privacy and security. Our Privacy Policy sets out our general handling information practices. We are committed to complying with both the Privacy Act and the National Privacy Principles.
Information Collected
The personal information collected and stored by us about you generally includes your name, address, contact details including phone, fax and email as provided to us. We require this information to enable us to contact you as part of our day to day business dealings and correspondence.
If you are a visitor to our website, we may collect your personal information for a number of reasons such as:
for the purposes of measurement, including the number of visitors to the site each day, the number of pages visited and the length of time people spend on those pages;
you may be enquiring about our services and will need to register your details with us so that the appropriate person can contact you.
We will use your personal information in accordance with the National Privacy Principles, such as for the purposes for which it is collected, to provide you with information on our products and services.
Security of Your Personal Information
Access to your personal information is limited to those who specifically need it to conduct their responsibilities. We also maintain physical security procedures to manage and protect the use and storage of paper records containing personal information.
Our staff are responsible for handling personal information in accordance with the Privacy Act.
We will take reasonable steps to destroy or permanently de-identify personal information when it is no longer required but having regard also to our obligation to maintain copies of files for 7 years.
Accuracy of Information
We will take reasonable steps to ensure that the information we hold about you is current, accurate and complete. If you believe that the information we have about you is not current, accurate and complete, we ask that you let us know.
Sharing and Disclosure of Information
We will not disclose information about you to a company that is not a related entity unless the disclosure is required or authorised by law, or you have consented to our disclosing the information about you. We may also need to disclose your information to law enforcement agencies, investigators and lawyers.
If You Have A Complaint
If you have a complaint about the privacy of your personal information, we ask that you write to us. We will promptly acknowledge and investigate complaints. At all times, we will respect and protect the privacy and confidentiality of personal information.
Barkus Doolan can be contacted by:
Email:
glenda@famlaw.com.au
